# 看嘛 这个就是野猪
Look! These are the pigs
# 是啊
Yeah
# 杀过这个野猪没有
Have you killed this kind of pigs before?
# 没有
Nope
# 没有杀过嘛
No?
# 就要那个小点的
Let's choose the smaller one
# 大的肉烤来不好吃
The meat of the bigger pig is not tasty after grilling
# 你说那条野猪有好重
How heavy is that pig?
# 那个啊
That one?
# 嗯 那个小的
Yeah, the smaller one
# 可能有40多斤
It might be about 40 plus jin
# 这个猪还是有点攻击性
These pigs are a little aggresive
# 它不是纯家猪也不是纯野猪
They are not totally domestic pigs or wild boars
# 它是野猪种性
But they have the characteristics of wild boars
# 嗯 是野猪跟家猪配出来的
Yeah, they are the hybrid offspring of wild boars and domestic pigs
# 杀这个猪一个人按得住不
Can a single person kill this pig by himself?
# 我一个人轻轻儿的就把它杀了
I can kill it easily by myself
# 金钩儿 钩住它提它起来割它一刀就解决了
Use the hooks (pigs killing tools) to hook it and lift it, cut it and it's done
# 这个跟华农的野猪不一样
These are different from the wild boars of Huanong brother
# 我的杀猪刀起码有它一半长
My pig killing knife is at least half as long as it's body
# 你一说它都吓到了
You scared the pig
# 慢点 我穿过来点不是你抬不起
Wait, I need to push the rod further or else you couldn't lift it
# 这有好重哦
This is so heavy
# 提一会儿就重了
Complaining the pig's heavy after lifting it for just a while?
# 慢一点四伯爷
Slow down, Uncle
# 69除开笼子46斤
It's around 46 jin
# 好
Okay
# 我说有40斤嘛
I said it, it's around 40 jin
# 40多
Yeah, 40+
# 哦哟
Oh!
# 好的 要得
Okay, it's done
# 好
Great
# 它不重还凶得很
It's not heavy but it's still so aggresive
# 你后面没有提起来
You didn't lift it tall enough back there
# 来
Here
# 诶呀
Aish!
# 我还没有喂过野猪第一次喂
I've never feed a wild boar before
# 这样它还多荣幸哦
Such an honour for the pig
# 那还用说 它是绝对享受
Yeah, this is an enjoyment for it
# 我修起还没喂过猪 第一次就喂这个野猪
I've never feed a pig since I started working, this is my first time to feed a pig
# 哦 出来了
Oh! It came out
# 羊肉烤起好吃
Grilled lamb is awesome
# 这个野性的野猪烤起可能更好吃哦
Grilled wild boar meat might be even tastier
# 隔几天你那天有空整来试一下嘛
You can come over and try the meat for the following few days when you are free
# 我杀了30、40年的野猪还没杀过野猪我拿来试一下看嘛
I have been a butcher for almost 30, 40 years but I've never tried to kill a wild boar
# （缺失）
I would like to try it
# 它都害怕了听你这么说
It's scared once it heard you said that
# 那个脑壳打整才不费力哟 平平顺顺的
This pig's head is flat, which makes it easier to be killed
# 你朝它念什么哦
Why are you talking to the pig?
# 那个苕藤是你的啊
Is that bush yours?
# 在外面拿的
I took it from the outside
# 不应该朝它念吧
He shouldn't be talking to the pig right
# 哦噢
Well yep
# 这又喂不了多久
We can't feed it any longer
# 我接着2、3天就弄来杀了烤来吃了
I will kill it and grill it to eat after a few days
# 我要是吃到这个野猪肉好吃你就要经常烤给我吃哦
If I like the taste of wild boar meat, you have to often grill it for me
# 经常 现在好贵哦
Often grill it? Wild boar is so expensive nowadays
# 再贵只要买得到就可以
As long as you can buy it, the price is not a problem
# 只要它吃起舒服管它钱不钱哦
As long as the taste is good, I dont really care about the money
# 40多斤还没有上次的羊子重
40 plus jin, it's not even as heavy as the lamb last time
# 猪脚杆拿来炖
We can stew the pork leg
# 有好多个人就炖好多坨
Stew as many pots of pig leg as the number of people
# 那这样我就去弄烧烤架
I will go and set up the barbeque rack then
# 那个架子小了烤它不下
The rack is too small, it can't fit the pig in
# 烤不到啊
Can't it?
# 嗯 烤不到重新焊个架子
Yeah, I need to weld a new rack
# 可以
Yeah